{
  "basicFront": "WHo is the strongest?",
  "basicBack": "I am"
},{
  "basicFront": "who is the coolest?",
  "basicBack": "me"
},{
  "basicFront": "Who is thirsty",
  "basicBack": "him"
},{
  "basicFront": "hello",
  "basicBack": "bye"
}{
  "basicFront": "Who is strong?",
  "basicBack": "me"
},{
  "basicFront": "Whos is weak",
  "basicBack": "him"
},{
  "basicFront": "who is far",
  "basicBack": "her"
},{
  "basicFront": "who is the bomb",
  "basicBack": "me"
}{
  "basicFront": "who is strong",
  "basicBack": "me"
},{
  "basicFront": "who is weak",
  "basicBack": "you"
},{
  "basicFront": "who is it",
  "basicBack": "me"
},{
  "basicFront": "who is there",
  "basicBack": "you"
}{
  "basicFront": "Who is it",
  "basicBack": "me"
},{
  "basicFront": "who is there",
  "basicBack": "you"
},{
  "basicFront": "who is here",
  "basicBack": "me"
},{
  "basicFront": "who is here",
  "basicBack": "you"
}{
  "basicFront": "heeeeewew",
  "basicBack": "dsffsdf"
},{
  "basicFront": "you go",
  "basicBack": "ok"
},{
  "basicFront": "i go",
  "basicBack": "okay"
},{
  "basicFront": "nooooo",
  "basicBack": "yesss"
}{
  "basicFront": "Who is at the zoo",
  "basicBack": "me"
},{
  "basicFront": "Who is at the mall?",
  "basicBack": "You"
},{
  "basicFront": "Who is at the church?",
  "basicBack": "me"
},{
  "basicFront": "Who is at the house",
  "basicBack": "You"
}{
  "clozeFront": "Yes",
  "clozeBack": "Hellloooo"
},{
  "clozeFront": "there",
  "clozeBack": "asdfs"
},{
  "clozeFront": "whyyy",
  "clozeBack": "nooo"
},{
  "clozeFront": "ok",
  "clozeBack": "Fine"
}{
  "clozeFront": "Whyyy",
  "clozeBack": "okay there"
},{
  "clozeFront": "hellooo",
  "clozeBack": "there we go"
},{
  "clozeFront": "Yes there",
  "clozeBack": "WHy dude"
},{
  "clozeFront": "Noooo broo",
  "clozeBack": "YEs bro"
}{
  "clozeFront": "Hey man whats up?",
  "clozeBack": "Hello"
},{
  "clozeFront": "Why are you here",
  "clozeBack": "because"
},{
  "clozeFront": "I like the zoo",
  "clozeBack": "yes"
},{
  "clozeFront": "Noooo",
  "clozeBack": "ok"
}{
  "basicFront": "sfsfawfewwe",
  "basicBack": "fawf"
},{
  "basicFront": "sdfewwf",
  "basicBack": "fwe"
},{
  "basicFront": "fewfew",
  "basicBack": "dff"
},{
  "basicFront": "efw",
  "basicBack": "sdfs"
}{
  "basicFront": "fsfwewfewf",
  "basicBack": "dsfs"
},{
  "basicFront": "Yes",
  "basicBack": "no"
},{
  "basicFront": "why",
  "basicBack": "beacue"
},{
  "basicFront": "sffe",
  "basicBack": "sdfs"
}{
  "basicFront": "fsfwafewf",
  "basicBack": "sf"
},{
  "basicFront": "sfewfwefe",
  "basicBack": "sfs"
},{
  "basicFront": "helllo",
  "basicBack": "man"
},{
  "basicFront": "swhew",
  "basicBack": "ok"
}{
  "clozeFront": "fdsfe",
  "clozeBack": "dsf"
},{
  "clozeFront": "fewewf",
  "clozeBack": "df"
},{
  "clozeFront": "Hellooo",
  "clozeBack": "yeah"
},{
  "clozeFront": "why",
  "clozeBack": "ok"
}